[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Простуда' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "風邪"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відрядження' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "出張"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відрядженняїхати у відрядження' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "出張します"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Будь здоров, бережи себе' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "お大事に"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Літати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "飛びます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Переносити, переставляти' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "運びます"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Повертати (на попереднє місце)' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "戻します"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Зірка' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "星"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Світ, блиск, промінь' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "光"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Небо' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "空"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Звук' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "音"
    }
]